Hello, my friends, and welcome again.
Exercise number 50 tells us to write a function to get the data value stored and then not at a given
index.
So in this exercise, we need to extract the data from the note at a given.
And so the user give us the index of the known and we get that data that's stored inside this node and
both iterative and recursive Mallette methods.
OK, so I need from you to post the video and think about this question.
We have solved this in the lecture, but we need to implement it in a real war exercise and to practice
more and Java.
And because they are both like 99 90 percent the same, but the same logic.
100 percent, OK.
The syntax may be different.
We have created these methods in their previous exercises, and we have tested them in the main.
We have created the note that contains that data and the next and I'm waiting for you to write your
questions.
Any recommendations?
Any review?
Please review us five stars on Udemy.
Do you support us making your videos and more tutorials and more exercises?
And I want from you to write this down and your copy book to review them before it at that that you
before any interview or any exam in university.
OK, so let's start making.
This method called Get and it took part in metered ends, and this and
this will solve.
Start by not current.
You need to get the current equal to have.
This is the have because we have declared it as a global variable for this class.
And count equal to zero.
I am making this for the index of not we are currently looking at.
And while we start by current does not equal to null,
then if the count equal equal to index, then it will return to return current the court date.
OK.
Again, count will be increased by + + + current.
I'm moving the cursor.
I'm moving the current to the next current next.
OK.
This is very simple.
I am making a loop that checks for the count equal equal to the index that we have passed and then return
encoding the date.
Otherwise, increase the count by one and current equal to the next to move that cursor to the next.
If we get to this line, that caller was for a nonexistence element.
So checking?
No, not found.
OK.
How to make it not found.
Assert we used to assert as false and return zero.
OK.
It's very simple.
I'm getting there.
Get an index called index.
We have created not.
And we called current and count equal to zero and moving this current Earth.
It's true that all the nods in order to find where is count equal to the end.
If it is not found, it will return zero.
OK, so let's go to the main and check for the existence.
Exercise 50.
OK.
Exercise 15, get there and no value.
Data
system that our friend and value of are the data of data is stored and.
No, no, no.
Like let me check for the node at Index three.
Okay, so link Atlas Dot Gath and and the index is 30.
And not number three, which is at index number two.
OK, so let's run and see.
We have here for one, five and three.
This is at Index zero descent index one and Index two, and this is at Index three.
OK.
The data stored in the node number three.
So this is zero.
This is numbers one, two and three is index zero, one and two.
And that data is equal to five.
So we have extracted it correctly using the iterative way and the next video, we are going to get this
instant data value and and recurring.